screamable.com 2014-06-18

# Privacy Policy - List Them Out

**** Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Advertisement policy**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Screamable has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Comments**  
We love comments, but any comments which is abusive, spread hatred, racial or any way hurting anyone opinion will never be entertained. We keep our comments moderated to maintain the integrity of individuals. We keep all the rights to accept or reject the comments

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting Screamable, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Email Addresses**  
Email address mentioned in the comment form will always be use for privacy and never be used for spamming or will never be sold or given to anyone.
